Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series X. Faculty and Staff
  - Biographical Files (including photographs)
    - Faculty
      - Pollock, Roy Van Horn (Box 28, Folder 47)
      - Poppensiek, George Charles (Box 28, Folder 48-49)
      - Poppensiek, George Charles (Box 29, Folder 1-8)
      - Postle, Donald S. (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Quick, Charles B. (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Quimby, Fred William (Box 29, Folder 11)
        1945-
      - Randolph, John F. (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Rassnick, Kenneth M. (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Ray, Jarna (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Rebhun, William Charles (Box 29, Folder 15)
        1947-1999
      - Reimers, Thomas J. (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Rendano, Victor Thomas, Jr. (Box 29, Folder 17)
        1946-
      - Reynolds, Arleigh J. (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Richards, James R. (Box 29, Folder 19)
        1948-2007
      - Rickard, Charles Glenwood (Box 29, Folder 20)
        1922-1993
        See also Alumni File 24-4-3326; Papers 24-7-3546; Memorial Statement
      - Riis, Ronald C. (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Roberts, Stephen James (Box 29, Folder 22-24)
        1915-2005
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-2903; Memorial Statement
      - Robertshaw, David (Box 29, Folder 25)
        1934-
      - Ross, George E., Jr. (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Rossiter, Christine (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Russell, David George (Box 29, Folder 28)
        1956-
      - Sack, Wolfgang Otto (Box 29, Folder 29)
        1928-2005
      - Saidla, John E. (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Scartlett, Janet [Scarlett-Kranz, Janet] (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Schat, Karel Antoni (Box 29, Folder 32)
      - Schermerhorn, Thomas (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - Schlafer, Donald Hughes (Box 29, Folder 34)
      - Schukken, Ynte Hein (Box 29, Folder 35)
      - Schryver, Herbert Francis (Box 29, Folder 36)
        See Also Alumni file 24-4-3326
      - Schwark, Wayne Stanley (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Scidmore, Marci A. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Scott, Danny W. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Scott, Fredric Winthrop (Box 30, Folder 4)
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History Collection 24-4-3349
      - Scrivani, Peter Vincent (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Sears, Philip (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Seeger, Christoph (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Sellers, Alvin F. (Box 30, Folder 8)
        1917-2008
      - Sevoian, Martin (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Sharp, Geoffrey W. G. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Sheffy, Ben E. (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Shelly, Sonjia (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Shin, Sang Jae (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Shively, James N. (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Short, Charles Everette (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
      - Simpson, Kenneth William (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Slauson, David Owen (Box 30, Folder 18)
        1943-
      - Smith, Donald Frederick (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Smith, Mary Cole (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Spaulding, Glen L. (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Spitzbergen, Jan (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Stehman, Susan (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Stephenson, Hadley Carruthers (Box 30, Folder 24)
        1893-1976
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3226; Memorial Statement
      - Stevens, Charles Edward (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Stinson, Al W. (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Straw, Barbara (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Stokol, Tracy (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Suarez, Susan S. (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Summer, William A. (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Sunderville, Earl (Box 30, Folder 31)
        1886-1958
      - Summers, Brian Alan (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Suter, Maja (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - Tamke, Patricia (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - Tapper, Daniel N. (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - Tasker, John Baker, Jr. (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - Tennant, Bud C. (Box 30, Folder 37-38)
      - Thompson, John C., Jr. (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - Todhunter, Rory James (Box 30, Folder 40)
        1952-
      - Torres, Alfonso (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - Trotter, Eric J. (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - Udall, Denny Hammond (Box 30, Folder 43)
        1874-1955
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 6641; Memorial Statement
      - Utermohlen, Virginia (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - Valentine, Beth A. (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - Visek, Willard J. (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - Volkmann, Dietert Hans (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - Wade, Susan E. (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - Walton, Donna (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - Wasserman, Robert H. (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - Wasserman, Robert H. (Box 30, Folder 51)
        See also Papers; 21-40-3519; Oral History Collection 24-4-3349
      - Wassom, Donald (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - Weiland, Gregory Arthur (Box 30, Folder 53)
        1950-
      - Wentworth, Richard A. (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - Wertz, Etta (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - Whittaker, Gary R. (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - White, Karl Karey, III (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - White, Maurice Edward "Pete" (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - Whitlock, John Hendrick (Box 30, Folder 59-60)
        1913-1994
        See also Papers 24-2-2223; Memorial Statement
      - Whitlock, Robert Henry (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - Williams, Walter Long (Box 30, Folder 62)
        1856-1945
        See also Oral History Collection (EP Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Wimsatt, William Abell (Box 30, Folder 63)
        1917-1985
      - Winand, Nina J. (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - Winter, Alexander Joseph (Box 30, Folder 65)
        See also Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - Woodie, James Brett (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - Woods, Gordon (Box 30, Folder 67)
      - Wootton, John F. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wurster, Nancy Burton (Box 31, Folder 2)
        1941-2006
      - Yeager, Amy (Dietze, Amy E. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Yen, Andrew (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - York, Charles J. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Zadoks, Ruth (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Zeissig, Alexander (Box 31, Folder 7)
        1901-1974
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 6642
      - Zimmer, James Francis (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Personnel
      - Residents, Interns (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Visiting Professors, Adjuncts, Fellows, Research Associates, Teaching Assistants (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Personnel
      - Brown, Robert Batson (Box 31, Folder 11)
        Assistant dean - administration
      - Edmonson, Katherine. (Box 31, Folder 12)
        Assistant dean - educational development, student services
      - Fowler, Ira (Box 31, Folder 13)
        Custodian
      - Griffith, Jeannie (Box 31, Folder 14)
        Staff writer
      - Haight, Helena H. (Box 31, Folder 15)
        Administrative manager
      - Hamilton, William (Box 31, Folder 16)
        Medical illustrator
      - Hendricks, Margaret A. "Peg" (Box 31, Folder 17)
        Assistant dean - public affairs and development
      - Huhta, Ina M. (Box 31, Folder 18)
        Accounts assistant
      - Kauber, Barbara M. (Box 31, Folder 19)
        Financial aid coordinator
      - Kelman, Eugenia (Box 31, Folder 20)
        Assistant dean - student services
      - Kent, Lindley C. (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Newson, Marion (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Quirk, Howard E. (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Selden, Shenetta (Box 31, Folder 24)
        Student services
      - Semmler, John Charles (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Smith, Robert F. (Box 31, Folder 26)
        Biomedical Communications
      - Sweet, Jai R. (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - Trethaway, Edward J. "Ned" (Box 31, Folder 28)
        Development
      - Voiland, Bonita S. (Box 31, Folder 29)
        Assistant dean - public affairs and development; See also Edward J. Trethaway Papers 41-5-2617
      - Webster, Robert James (Box 31, Folder 30)
        Engineer
      - Wheeler, Gene (Box 31, Folder 31)
        Assistant dean - financial affairs
      - Willis, George (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - Wilson, Archie (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Library Personnel
      - Burnett, Nellie Marie Reed (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Heyns, Erla P. (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - Purrington, Alice (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Reinap, Mia (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Whitaker, Susanne K. (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Williams, Edith Clifford (Box 31, Folder 39-43)
    - Clinical and Technical Personnel
      - Alo, Debbie (Box 31, Folder 44)
        Clinical support
      - Angstrom, Clement I. (Box 31, Folder 45)
        Veterinarian; Poultry diagnostic lab
      - Asmua, Henry (Box 31, Folder 46)
        18??-1939
        Farrier: See also Faculty file
      - Asmus, Henry (Box 31, Folder 47)
        Farrier; See also Faculty file
      - Bartholomew, Patricia (Box 31, Folder 48)
      - Bigler, Laura (Box 31, Folder 49)
        Veterinarian; Diagnostic lab
      - Blackedge, George (Box 31, Folder 50)
        Graduate student
      - Caldwell, Katie (Box 31, Folder 51)
      - Conklin, Marshall "Buster" (Box 31, Folder 52)
        1926-2011
        Farrier
      - Craig, Peter H. (Box 31, Folder 53)
        Veterinarian
      - Fairbrother, ? (Box 31, Folder 54)
      - Fielder, H. G. (Box 31, Folder 55)
      - Hoshino, Takata? (Box 31, Folder 56)
        Microbiology
      - Johndrew, O. F., Jr. (Box 31, Folder 57)
      - Joo, Kim (Box 31, Folder 58)
        Physiology
      - Kelly, Diane (Box 31, Folder 59)
      - Koland, ? (Box 31, Folder 60)
      - Kraft, Marie (Box 31, Folder 61)
        Laboratory technician
      - Kramer, Larry (Box 31, Folder 62)
      - Layton, Eugene W. "Gene" (Box 31, Folder 63)
      - Lopes, ? (Box 31, Folder 64)
        Baker Institute
      - Medway, William (Box 31, Folder 65)
      - Monlux, William S. (Box 31, Folder 66)
      - Mowers, Harold (Box 31, Folder 67)
      - Olm, Dale (Box 31, Folder 68)
      - Rich, Lon D (Box 31, Folder 69)
      - Rivkin, Lawrence S. (Box 31, Folder 70)
        Pharmacist
      - Ryan, Gerald (Box 31, Folder 71)
        Radiological technician
      - Schultz, Ronald (Box 31, Folder 72)
      - Shannon, Kevin (Box 31, Folder 73)
      - Weiss, Richard C. (Box 31, Folder 74)
      - Weisman, Ziva M. (Box 31, Folder 75)
        Research associate
      - White, Gershorn Franklin (Box 31, Folder 76)
      - Wildenstein, Michael Jon (Box 31, Folder 77)
      - Williams, Jim (Box 31, Folder 78)
      - Williams, Raymond C. (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Non-Cornell
      - Amand, Wilbur (Box 31, Folder 80)
      - Barber, Clifford W. (Box 31, Folder 81)
      - Benjamine, Maxine (Box 31, Folder 82)
      - Callis, Jerry J. (Box 31, Folder 83)
      - Detweiler, David K. (Box 31, Folder 84)
      - Dunlop, Robert H. (Box 31, Folder 85)
      - Gordon, Ruth (Box 31, Folder 86)
      - Goss, Leonard J. (Box 31, Folder 87)
      - Kennedy, Peter (Box 31, Folder 88)
      - Leathem, James H. (Box 31, Folder 89)
      - Meyer, Hermann (Box 31, Folder 90)
      - Patterson, Fred D. (Box 31, Folder 91)
      - Paine, Loyal C. (Box 31, Folder 92)
      - Pilchard, Edwin Ivan (Box 31, Folder 93)
      - Preuss, Fritz R. (Box 31, Folder 94)
      - Sanjar, M. (Box 31, Folder 95)
      - Saunders, Leon Z. (Box 31, Folder 96)
      - Twardock, Arthur R. (Box 31, Folder 97)
      - West, R. Leland (Box 31, Folder 98)
      - Wojciechowski, Krzysztof Jan (Box 31, Folder 99)
  - Millennium Video Project Interviews
    - Millennium Video Project - General Planning, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 100)
    - Millennium Video Project - Franklin M. Loew Interview, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 101)
    - Millennium Video Project - Edward C. Melby Jr. Interview, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 102)
    - Millennium Video Project - Robert D. Phemister Interview, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 103)
  - Faculty Portraits
    - Appel, Max J. G. (Box 32)
      1964 - 1997
    - Baker, James A. (Box 32)
      1947 - 1975
    - Baker, James A. (Box 32)
    - Baker, Donald W. (Box 32)
      1929 - 1965
      Pathology and Bacteriology
    - Bergman, Emmett N. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1989
    - Bloom, Stephen (Box 32)
      1991-2011
      Microbiology and Immunology
    - Blue, Julia Tait (Box 32)
      1980 - 2002
      Population Medicine and Diagnostic Science
    - Boyer, Jr., Clyde I. (Box 32)
      1952 - 1980
      Laboratory Animal Medicine
    - Brunner, Michael A. (Box 32)
      1980 - 1999
    - Burner, Dorsey W. (Box 32)
      "1931 - 1937 1949-1972"
    - Calnek, Bruce W. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1995
      Avian and Aquatic Medicine
    - Campbell, S. Gordon (Box 32)
      1967 - 1997
    - Carmichael, Leland E. (Box 32)
      1956 - 1997
      Clinical Sciences
    - Comar, Cyril L. (Box 32)
      1957 - 1975
      Physical Biology
    - Concannon, Patrick W. (Box 32)
      1972 - 1999
      Biomedical Sciences - Physiology
    - Cooper, Barry J. (Box 32)
      1977 - 2002
      Biomedical Sciences
    - Corradino, Robert A. (Box 32)
      1966 - 1999
    - Cummings, John F. (Box 32)
      1976 - 1996
      Anatomy
    - Danks, A. Gordon (Box 32)
      1936 - 1969
      Large Animal Surgery - Student Administration
    - de Lahunta, Alexander (Box 32)
      1960 - 2005
      Anatomy - Neurology
    - DeNoronha, Fernando (Box 32)
      1968 - 1995
    - Dobson, Alan (Box 32)
    - Dukes, H. Hugh (Box 32)
      1932 - 1960
    - Dye, J. A. (Box 32)
      1940 - 1960
    - Evans, Howard E. (Box 32)
      1950 - 1986
    - Fabricant, Julius (Box 32)
      1946 - 1985
      Avian Diseases
    - Field, Lincoln E. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1971
      Large Animal Medicine, Obstatrics and Surgery
    - Fincher, Myron G. (Box 32)
      1920 - 1965
      Medicine and Obstetrics
    - Fox, Francis H. (Box 32)
      1947 - 1992
      Large Animal Clinic
    - Gasteiger, Edgan L. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1987
    - Geary, Jack C. (Box 32)
      1952 - 1959
      Radiology
    - Georgi, Jay R. (Box 32)
      1953 - 1989
      Parasitology
    - Gillespie, James H. (Box 32)
      1946 - 1986
    - Gilman, H. L. (Box 32)
      1919 - 1962
      Bacteriology and Pathology
    - Guthrie, Richard S. (Box 32)
      1956-1972
      Large Animal Medicine, Obstetrics and Surgery
    - Habel, Robert E. (Box 32)
      1947 - 1978
    - Hall, Charles E. (Box 32)
      1969 - 1988
    - Hansel, William (Box 32)
      1946 - 1989
    - Henion, John D. (Box 32)
      1976 - 2002
    - Hillman, Robert B. (Box 32)
      1964 - 1995
    - Hitchner, Stephen B. (Box 32)
      1966 - 1981
    - Holmes, Dorothy F. (Box 32)
      1964 - 1991
    - Houpt, Katherine A. (Box 32)
      1975 - 2009
    - Houpt, T. Richard (Box 32)
      1971 - 2001
    - Jacobson, Richard H. (Box 32)
      1977 - 2000
    - Johnson, Seth D. (Box 32)
      1929 - 1969
    - Kallfelz, Francis (Box 32)
      1973 - 2008
    - King, John M. (Box 32)
      1968 - 1998
      Pathology
    - Kirk, Robert W. (Box 32)
      1952 - 1985
      Small Animal Medicine
    - Krook, Lennart P. (Box 32)
    - Lee, Kyu M. (Box 32)
      1963 - 1987
    - Leibovitz, Louis (Box 32)
      1963 - 1988
    - Lengemann, Frederick W. (Box 32)
      1958 - 1988
    - Leonard, Ellis P. (Box 32)
      1948 - 1969
      Small Animal Medicine and Surgery
    - Levine, P. Philip (Box 32)
      1934 - 1972
    - Lewis, Robert M. (Box 32)
      1975 - 2000
    - Lowe, John E. (Box 32)
      1959 - 1991
      Diagnostic Laboratory
    - Ludders, John (Box 32)
      1989-2011
    - McEntee, Kenneth (Box 32)
      1947 - 1980
    - McGregor, Douglas (Box 32)
      1976-2010
    - Miller, Malcolm E. (Box 32)
    - Minor, Ronald (Box 32)
      1976 - 2007
    - Naqi, Syed A. (Box 32)
      1987 - 2002
    - Nathanielz, Peter W. (Box 32)
      1982 - 2002
    - Norcross, Neil (Box 32)
      1960 - 1994
    - Olafson, Peter (Box 32)
      1926 - 1965
    - Page, Rodney (Box 32)
      1999-2010
    - Pauli, Bendicht (Box 32)
      1987-2011
      Molecular Medicine
    - Peckham, Malcolm C. (Box 32)
      1950 - 1984
    - Postle, Donald S. (Box 32)
    - Quimby, Fred W. (Box 32)
      1979 - 2001
      Biomedical Sciences - Laboratory Animal Medicine
    - Rebhun, William C. (Box 32)
      1976 - 1999
    - Reimers, Thomas J. (Box 32)
      1978 - 1999
    - Rendano, Jr., Victor T. (Box 32)
    - Riis, Ronald (Box 32)
      1974 - 2007
    - Roberts, Stephen J. (Box 32)
      1942 - 1972
    - Robertshaw, David (Box 32)
      1987-2001
    - Sack, Wolfgang O. (Box 32)
    - Saidla, John E. (Box 32)
      1988 - 2000
    - Schat, Karel (Box 32)
      1978-2011
      Micro and Immun
    - Schryver, Herbert F. (Box 32)
      1966 - 1990
    - Scott, Fredric W. (Box 32)
      1968 - 1996
    - Sellers, Alvin F. (Box 32)
      1960 - 1985
    - Sheffy, Ben E. (Box 32)
      1955 - 1985
    - Shin, Sang Jae (Box 32)
      1973 - 2005
      Bacteriology
    - Short, Charles E. (Box 32)
      1977 - 1999
    - Stephenson, Hadley C. (Box 32)
      1919 - 1953
    - Summers, Brian A. (Box 32)
      1976 - 2006
    - Tapper, Daniel N. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1996
    - Wasserman, Robert H. (Box 32)
      1957 - 1997
    - Whitlock, John H. (Box 32)
      1944 - 1979, 1971-1976
      Parasitology - University Trustee
    - Winter, Alexander J. (Box 32)
      1963 - 1995
    - Wootton, John F. (Box 32)
      1962 - 2003
    - Dr. Lowe placing a beef bull on a surgical table to remove an interdigital growth on the animal's foot in Schurman Hall/Veterinary Hospital., 1960s? (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Training and Activities of the Veterinarian tree (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Public Health activities (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Fred Kilborne, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Faculty in front of Bailey Hall, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Faculty: James Law Hall; V.A. Moore and J. Law at bottom, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Small portraits of students (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - 3 rows of faculty outside building, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Faculty, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Faculty, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Series XI. Offices and Functions
  - Admissions (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Curriculum (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Environmental Health and Safety (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Financial Aid (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Study (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Medical Computing Facility, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Administration (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Series XII. Programs and Conferences
  - Animal Pain and Its Control, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Conference on Public Health (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Cornell at Saratoga (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Cornell at Saratoga, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Symposium for Dog Enthusiasts, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Equine Practitioners Conference, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Farriers Conference (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Fred Scott Feline Symposium (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Fred Scott Feline Symposium, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - High School Natural Science Program-General, 1969-1964 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - High School Natural Science Program-Packet, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - High School Natural Science Program-Packet, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - International Equine Neurology Conference, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - International Symposium on BVD Virus, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - James Law Lecture Programs (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Leadership Program, 1991,2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Poultry Disease School (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Radiation Biology Institutes, 1965-1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ruminant Health-Nutrition Conference (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Smith Kilborne Program, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Summer Institute Programs (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Veterinary Dermatology Conference, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Veterinary Dermatology Conference, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Veterinary Laser Surgery for the Small Animal Practice, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Workshops and Conferences (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Farm Radio Programs, 1943-1946 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Photographs and Slides
  - Congress Banquet -- International Veterinary Congress, New York, Aug. 16, 1934, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Luncheon in honor of Prof. Dr. Robert Von Ostertag, International Veterinary Congress, Aug. 15, 1934, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Dinner tendered to members by Borden Farm Products, Sheffield Farms, and Dairymen's League Co-Op Assoc., Aug. 17, 1934, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - AVMA Convention, Nashville, TN; Dr. Daniel E. Salmon seated left of center, 1897 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - AVMA Convention, Indianapolis, Indiana, Sept 26-31, 1912; 6 rows; women in 2nd row with large hats., 1912 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - AVMA Squibb Party for Deans, 1958, Philadelphia; 30 small photos in rows., 1958 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - NYSVMS meeting, Sept 1903; triangular rows behind Clinic Building; James Law in center left front in white suit, 1903 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Annual meeting Hotel Utica, July 30-Aug 1, 1912, 1912 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting in Ithaca in front of James Law Hall; James Law is center right., 1912-1915 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, Ithaca, Aug 1-3, 1916 in front of James Law Hall, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Rows in front of James Law Hall; 1 row kneeling; 2 standing, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 3 rows in front of James Law Hall, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 2nd class, July 13-17, 1964; Principles of Meat Hygiene and Inspection. Prof. Peter Olafson and Dean George Poppensiek seated in center., 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 11th Conference of Supervising Veterinarians, Sept. 30, 1964, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - State and federal veterinarians conference, 1944; 5 rows of front of Moore Laboratory, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Series XIII. Graphics and Audiovisual Material
  - Postcards featuring the College (Box 21)
  - Wearers of the "C" photo album (Vet students who participated in sports), 1902-1939 (Box 14)
  - Wearers of the "C" photo album Vet students who participated in sports), 1940-1961 (Box 14)
  - Posters (Box 9)
  - Franklin Loew Memorial Display, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Deans Hagan and Poppensiek Caricature (in pastels), 1960s (Box 9)
  - Place Cards for Honor Day - Caricature of the Faculty, by Vincent Paciello, 1940 (Box 16)
  - Place Cards for Honor Day - Animals, by Rebecca Gifford, 1940 (Box 17)
  - Pages and loose photos from Edwin R. Jackson's scrapbook, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Glass plate negatives of college buildings, equipment and activity, including two large negatives of students, faculty, and James Law gathered for a lesson in equine surgery., 1910 (Box 22)
  - Extremely large photo of F.L. Kilborne (Map-case Folder 3)
  - External Parasites Infesting the Dog (Map-case Folder 1)
  - Two sketches of the architecture of the Veterinary School (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Large hand drawn illustration of an internal organ (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Large Image of T. Smith (1859-1934) (Map-case Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Films, some of college scenes, some of faculty research, some unidentified (Box 10,11,14,15)
  - Several film reels, including the ones put into the cornerstone of the new Veterinary College, and other assorted film rolls, 1953-1958 (Box 10)
  - Film reels on Gains Dog Research Center,Rabies, and assorted other film reels, 1952-1958 (Box 11)
  - Studies of Feline Respiratory Viruses in Tissue Culture Systems (Box 14)
    Photographs
  - Film reels on faculty and "71 Valiant Years", 1934-1935 (Box 15)
  - Film reel of Faculty, 1932; F-1617 (Box 37)
  - Caricatures made for Honor Day Banquet by Vincent Paciello, 1940 (Box 16)
  - Animal Table Decorations for Honor Day Banquet by Rebecca Gifford, 1940 (Box 17)
  - Historical Post Cards (Box 21)
- Series XIV. Miscellaneous
  - Honor Code (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Logo, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Medical College (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Polo (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Veterinary Education (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Veterinary Education-"Suggestive Comments on Veterinary Education..." by Alumni, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Veterinary Profession (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Veterinary Reserve Corps and ROTC (Box 6, Folder 6)